<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fajrin Nugraha</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fajrin Nugraha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Buy Me a Coffee, Feed My Creativity</title>
      <link>/articles/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/article/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! If you&amp;rsquo;ve stumbled upon my portfolio website and you&amp;rsquo;re feeling particularly generous, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say no to a donation for a cup of coffee! You see, I&amp;rsquo;m a writer, and my brain runs on caffeine. Without it, I&amp;rsquo;m basically a zombie with a keyboard.
But really, any amount would be greatly appreciated. Even if it&amp;rsquo;s just enough for a sip of coffee, I&amp;rsquo;ll still be over the moon. And who knows, maybe that sip will be enough to spark a brilliant idea for my next article or project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Quality and Compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/article-intern/</guid>
      <description>As a Quality Control Intern at Murinda, I had the opportunity to participate in projects for JGC Indonesia and Mitsui E&amp;amp;S. In this role, I contributed to the quality control process and ensured compliance with project specifications. This allowed me to develop valuable skills in quality control and project management.
During my time at Murinda, I assisted in inspecting and testing products to ensure compliance with quality standards. This gave me hands-on experience with quality control procedures and principles, which I learned and applied in a practical environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kopi Tujuhdua</title>
      <link>/portfolios/article-kopi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolios/article-kopi/</guid>
      <description>Kopi Tujuhdua is a coffee brand that was founded and managed by me as entrepreneur during the Covid-19 pandemic. With a passion for entrepreneurship and a love for coffee, the founder saw an opportunity to turn their passion into a business.
Taking on all aspects of the business, including branding, marketing, and production, the founder developed and executed a successful marketing plan that resulted in increased brand awareness and sales. Through a combination of social media marketing, partnerships with local businesses, and a commitment to quality, Kopi Tujuhdua quickly gained a loyal following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading Design and Documentation Team for One Love Award Event</title>
      <link>/portfolios/article-olaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolios/article-olaf/</guid>
      <description>As the head of the design and documentation team, I played a crucial role in the success of the One Love Award event at Telkom University. I was responsible for creating visually engaging materials such as banners, posters, certificates, and social media content, while adhering to the event&amp;rsquo;s branding guidelines and theme.
Working closely with the organizing committee, I ensured timely and high-quality delivery of all materials. This project helped me develop valuable skills in project management, communication, and teamwork, while also gaining an appreciation for the importance of visual communication and documentation in successful events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering Digital Public Relations Student Association</title>
      <link>/portfolios/article-hima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolios/article-hima/</guid>
      <description>During my time as a member of the design team in the Communication and Information Department, I contributed to the pioneering of the Digital Public Relations Student Association. I utilized my design skills to create engaging media that effectively conveyed information and resonated with the target audience. Through collaboration with fellow designers, I helped expand the department&amp;rsquo;s reach and influence among students, contributing to the overall success and growth of the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
