<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Fajrin Nugraha</title>
    <link>/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Fajrin Nugraha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Buy Me a Coffee, Feed My Creativity</title>
      <link>/articles/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/article/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! If you&amp;rsquo;ve stumbled upon my portfolio website and you&amp;rsquo;re feeling particularly generous, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say no to a donation for a cup of coffee! You see, I&amp;rsquo;m a writer, and my brain runs on caffeine. Without it, I&amp;rsquo;m basically a zombie with a keyboard.
But really, any amount would be greatly appreciated. Even if it&amp;rsquo;s just enough for a sip of coffee, I&amp;rsquo;ll still be over the moon. And who knows, maybe that sip will be enough to spark a brilliant idea for my next article or project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Quality and Compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/article-intern/</guid>
      <description>As a Quality Control Intern at Murinda, I had the opportunity to participate in projects for JGC Indonesia and Mitsui E&amp;amp;S. In this role, I contributed to the quality control process and ensured compliance with project specifications. This allowed me to develop valuable skills in quality control and project management.
During my time at Murinda, I assisted in inspecting and testing products to ensure compliance with quality standards. This gave me hands-on experience with quality control procedures and principles, which I learned and applied in a practical environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
